Led by the omniscient Spirit of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua moves around the congregation,
revealing prophetic insight into people's lives that exposes the root of their problems,
releasing them for their deliverance.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prophecy And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on.
You are using one honey.
Yes, sir.
You know honey? Honey that they lick.
As I touched you, I felt there was honey given to you by a spiritualist.
Yes, sir.
For what?
Fruit of the womb; they said I should be taking it.
But the way you are taking it is not normal because you are now using it to rub your private part.
Exactly, sir.
How can you use honey to rub your private part?
Come on.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
After the prophecy, Mrs Joy Nkeke rushes to the toilet to check herself
and discovers that truly, a spiritual operation has taken place
and her menstruation that had seized for many years has returned.
A few minutes after her deliverance, Mrs Joy Nkeke came forward to share her instant testimony.
Let's listen to her.
Man of God, after you prayed for me,
the menstruation I had not seen for four years, I have started seeing it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank You, Jesus.
For four years, you had not been seeing your menstruation?
Yes. After taking that honey, for four years, it ceased.
After taking that honey, the menstruation ceased?
Yes. I have started seeing it now.
After the prayer?
Exactly.
Thank You, Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Joy Nkeke, I am a Nigerian. I came from Denmark.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was ceased menstruation for four years.
Last week Sunday, the man of God prophesied to me that
I was using honey given to me by a spiritualist.
I said, yes.
After the man of God laid hands on me, I started seeing my menstruation immediately.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Mrs Joy Nkeke
Prophecy Testimony
You made it clear that the problem that brought you to The SCOAN last Sunday
was ceased menstruation for four years.
While you were in the midst of the people during the laying of hands
by the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua, he came exactly to where you were
and prophesied to you that you were given honey, which you confirmed to be true.
Instantly he laid hands on you, your menstruation that had been seized for four years started flowing.
Could you tell us how it all started?
It all started when I was looking for the fruit of the womb.
So, I went to a spiritualist who gave me some honey.
After taking the honey, I started eating in the dream;
masquerades were chasing me in the dream.
It looked as if my problem increased.
My menstruation ceased.
Last week Sunday when the man of God laid his hand on me and prophesied to me,
I started seeing my menstruation immediately.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Mrs Joe Nkeke
Prophecy Testimony
I want to say, "Thank You, Jesus". If you are looking for a solution, Jesus is the solution.
Thank You, Jesus, for all you have done in my life.
You heard it from her. With what the Lord has done in her life.
Her menstruation that had seized for four years started flowing instantly
the message of prophecy came forth and she received a touch from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
That was the end of the seized menstruation, to the glory of God.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
TT: unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 25/08/2018